▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 1/4决赛
斯瓦泰克 vs 莱巴金娜 · 赛后场上采访
It's always a huge disappointment
这总是让人非常失望
when an opponent has to retire
当对手不得不
from a match.
退出比赛
It's not the kind of win that you want to see.
这不是任何人想看到的胜利
Yeah, of course.
是的 当然
Honestly, I was feeling anxious just looking
老实说 光是看着
at this situation.
这个情况我就很焦虑
So I hope Elena will be fine and obviously
所以我希望伊莲娜没事 显然
the next tournament is the priority.
下一站赛事才是重点
I know this one is important as well,
我知道这一站也很重要
but US Open is US Open
但美网就是美网
and I hope she's going to be ready
我希望她能准备好
for that because she's also super close
因为她现在也非常接近
to being number one in the world.
世界第一
So it's a shame
所以真的很遗憾
because I felt we were playing
因为我觉得我们本来
a good match.
打得很好
But health is a priority,
但健康更重要
so I hope she's going to be okay,
所以我希望她会没事
really.
真的
We do, we hope she's going to be okay.
我们也希望她会没事
And if Elena's listening,
如果伊莲娜正在听
we do wish you a speedy recovery.
祝你早日康复
Let's take this opportunity
我们就借这个机会
to spend a couple of minutes with you, talk
再和你聊几分钟
about the kind of tennis you're playing now.
谈谈你现在的网球状态
You seem that you're in a zone,
你好像进入了自己的节奏
you're in a good place,
整个人状态很好
a smile when you walk out on court,
走上球场时也带着笑容
you're back here as defending champion
你以卫冕冠军身份回到这里
to the heart of tennis.
回到网球之心
How special to be back here in Mason,
再回到俄亥俄州梅森
Ohio?
有多特别
Yeah, I feel great.
是的 我感觉很棒
I feel ready to play my best game
我已经准备好拿出最佳状态
and the last weeks have been giving me
最近几周也给了我
a lot of confidence.
很多信心
So I'm happy to be here playing good tennis
所以我很高兴能在这里
that I like and I enjoy and for sure it's fun.
打自己喜欢的网球 享受比赛
Okay, so we have not till 8 30 until
好 男单要到八点半才上场
the guys come out.
还有些时间
So can you and I play singles for a little
要不要和我打一会儿单打
while and you can help me with my volume?
顺便帮我练练嗓门
Just got to ask.
总得问问
I mean, I'm kidding.
开玩笑的
Will you sign some tennis balls for us?
能帮我们签几个网球吗
Before you do real quick, Jessica Pegula,
签之前 快问一句 佩古拉
you've played her a lot.
你们交手过很多次
You know her game very well.
你很熟悉她的打法
She's tough. You're tough.
她很难缠 你也一样
What do we have in store
看你们交手时
when we watch you play Jessie?
我们会看到什么
Well, she's a great competitor.
她是个很棒的竞争者
And, you know,
你知道吧
I feel like we've been on Tour for...
我想我们在巡回赛很久了
We've been playing many matches
我们已经打过很多场比赛
where we had our best games like clashing.
两人状态最佳时正面碰上
And it's always such a tough match.
每次都是非常艰难的比赛
It went both ways.
彼此都赢过
Many three-setters.
也多次打满三盘
So I'm excited to play this match
所以我很期待这场比赛
because for sure it's going to be a challenge
因为对我来说一定会是挑战
for me.
对我来说
She has a great game for hard courts.
她的打法很适合硬地
And yeah, it's going to be a good semi
这一定会是一场精彩的半决赛
for sure.
肯定会很精彩
All right. We wish you best of luck
好的 祝你
in the semis.
半决赛好运
Welcome back to Cincy.
欢迎回到辛辛那提
Your defending champion.
有请你们的卫冕冠军
Everyone, Iga Swiatek.
各位 伊加·斯瓦泰克
Let's get some autographed tennis balls.
来签几个网球吧